Guide to the United Federation of Teachers Photographs PHOTOS 019
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series I: New York Teacher Photograph Files, 1951-1987.
  - Subseries I:L: Demonstrations/Rallies/Parades.
    - Sub-subseries I:L:3: Miscellaneous
      - Solzhenitsyn Demonstration, Mar 1974 (Item 2897)
      - [UFT?:] Paraprofessional Demonstration, Apr 1974 (Item 2987)
      - Rally to support continued superintendancy of Rhoda Lansky, Apr 1974 (Item 2995)
      - Rally Protesting Exclusion of Israel from UNESCO, Feb 1975 (Item 3528)
      - IUD Rally, Apr 1975 (Item 3614)
      - Mental Health Demonstration, Jun 1975 (Item 3732)
      - Mental Health Fund Demonstration, Jun 1975 (Item 3772)
      - Transit Workers Demonstration, Aug 1975 (Item 3823)
      - Student Demonstration in front of Governor's office to protest overcrowded conditions in the classroom, Oct 1975 (Item 3920)
      - Zionism Rally, Nov 1975 (Item 3969)
      - Picketing by members of the Federation of Catholic Teachers paid off as the teachers forged a new contract with the Archdiocese of New York to avert a strike, Nov 16, 1975 (Item 3910)
      - Stavisky-Goodman, Rally, 1976 (Item 4265)
      - CUNY and SUNY Demonstrate to protest budget cuts, Mar 1976 (Item 4124)
      - Russel Stover Candies Boycott, Apr 1976 (Item 4397)
      - Firestone Products, Rubber Workers picketing of Firestone outlets and retail stores, May 1976 (Item 4275)
      - Rally, Family Care, Jun 1976 (Item 4554)
      - Bicentennial Parade, Jun 20, 1976 (Item 4479)
      - Amalgamated Clothing Workers Demonstration, Dec 1976 (Item 1696)
      - Labor, Wilkes Barre Federal Workers Protest, 1979 (Item 4244)
      - Labor, Iron Workers protest American hostage in Iran situation, Jan 1980 (Item 4244)
      - Demonstration, Budget Cuts [Includes but may not be limited to:] Gaeta, Anthony, Mar 1980 (Item 776)
      - United Parents Association Rally with Ted Ellsberg CSA, Apr 1980 (Item 1427)
      - Save Our Schools Rally [Includes but may not be limited to:] DePesa, Jean (President United Parents Association); Gaeta, Anthony, May 1980 (Item 776)
      - United Farm Workers Lettuce Boycott, "Red Coach", May 1980 (Item 3891)
      - Pension Supplementation Rally, Jun 1980 (Item 5245)
      - Carter, James Earl (President), rally for, Oct 16, 1980 (Item 4169)
      - Texas International Airlines, Picketing creation of New York Air, Runaway shop, Dec 1980 (Item 5372)
      - Pension Supplementation Rally, Signing of Law: Cary and Silverman, 1981 (Item 5245)
      - Feldman, Sandra, Rally against Reagan Budget Cuts, May 1981 (Item 852)
      - Retired Teachers, Save Our Social Security Rally, Jun 18, 1981 (Item 3113)
      - Eli Whitney Vocational HS [Connecticut?], picketing re: fired teacher, Jan 1982 (Item 5507)
      - Shapiro, Elliott, Demonstration, undated (Item 155)
      - Protest on unreal credit requirements, undated (Item 168)
      - Teacher-Parent protest at "School With Hope", undated (Item 170)
      - Singer Bowl Rally, undated (Item 250)
      - Shapiro, Morris, Trade Teachers Demonstration, undated (Item 406)
      - Student Protest Demonstrations, undated (Item 416)
      - Index Bill demonstration, undated (Item 519)
      - United Parents Association, Save Our Schools Rally, undated (Item 1427)
      - ACWA Members protest foreign made clothing from countries who pay low wages and then sell garments at prices comparable to American made, undated (Item 1803)
      - Teacher Demonstrations, undated (Item 2664)
      - Teacher Rallies (unidentified), undated (Item 3272)
      - Rally, IUD, undated (Item 3821)
      - Campbell, Claude Addresses demonstrators outside building of higher ed, undated (Item 4324)
      - Jewish Labor Rally, Tel Aviv, undated (Item 4754)
      - Demonstrations, unidentified, undated (Item 5634)
      - Phelps Dodge Campaign [United Steelworkers, Support the Copper Strikers], undated (Item 5653)
  - Subseries I:M: Schools/Students/Teachers.
    - Sub-subseries I:M:1: Schools and Students
      - Morales, Tania (Regent Scholarship Winner) and parents, Feb 6, 1970 (Item 1167)
      - United Federation of Future Teachers, meeting, Apr 22, 1971 (Item 1464)
      - Restructuring the Middle Schools story, Aug 1971 (Item 1675)
      - HS Auxiliary Services, Oct 10, 1971 (Item 2702)
      - Early Childhood Centers, Nov 1971 (Item 1651)
      - Puerto Rico Discovery Day Programs (all schools, 1972) (Item 2051)
      - Center for Multiple Handicapped Children, Apr 21, 1972 (Item 1744)
      - Industrial Arts exhibition, May 1972 (Item 1810)
      - Center for Multiple Handicapped Children, May 7, 1972 (Item 1744)
      - Early Childhood Centers, Jun 1972 (Item 1651)
      - Student Council Meeting, Mar 1973 (Item 2269)
      - State PTA awards 25 College Scholarships to future teachers, May 1973 (Item 2514)
      - Occupational Training Center Annual Field Day, Jun 24, 1973 (Item 1045)
      - Reading Conference, High School Students at Hall of Board of Ed, Nov 1973 (Item 2745)
      - Classroom Photos, Children, Mar 1974 (Item 2896)
      - Shanker, Al with Student NYSTA, Mar 1974 (Item 2907)
      - Classroom Organizations, informal, Plattsburgh, NY, May 1974 (Item 3072)
      - West Junior High, Auditorium Morning Session, May 1974 (Item 3077)
      - NYSEE Students Conference, Oct 1974 (Item 3445)
      - NYSEE, Marguerite Belden, Education Issues Conference, Oct 1974 (Item 3502)
      - Institute of Industrial Relations gives class on labor relations, Jan 1975 (Item 3523)
      - Hirsh, Barbara with Bryna Levine, students in Intensive Language Program, Mar 1975 (Item 3725)
      - Student Lab, May 1975 (Item 3713)
      - Sterling HS [New Jersey?] Bicentennial Program, May 1975 (Item 3768)
      - Classroom Photos, Jul 1975 (Item 3806)
      - Student Demonstration in front of Governor's office to protest overcrowded conditions in the classroom, Oct 1975 (Item 3920)
      - Class Size, Oct 1975 (Item 3926)
      - NYSEE [New York Students for Effective Education] RA, Mar 1976 (Item 4177)
      - Westinghouse Winners, Mar 1976 (Item 4338)
      - Early Childhood Learning Center, Apr 1976 (Item 4269)
      - Happy Birthday, America Pageant, Apr 1976 (Item 4288)
      - NY Students win science talent honors, Apr 1976 (Item 4392)
      - Student Art Festival, May 1976 (Item 4254)
      - Ability Counts Winners, May 1976 (Item 4420)
      - Elementary School Physical Education awards ceremony, Jun 1976 (Item 4474)
      - Learning Fair, Jun 1976 (Item 4555)
      - Altneu, Sylvia, Career Exploration Day, Jun 13, 1976 (Item 4450)
      - Food Day Observance, Jun 13, 1976 (Item 4456)
      - Bicentennial Parade, Jun 20, 1976 (Item 4479)
      - Second Annual Adolescents' Learning Fair, Jun 27, 1976 (Item 4493)
      - SUNY/CUNY Meeting with Hobart and Shanker, Jan 1977 (Item 4748)
      - Sterling HS [New Jersey?] Fair 78, 1978 (Item 3768)
      - Feldman, Sandra, Elementary Schools, 1979 (Item 2939)
      - School Safety, Antonia Cortese, 1979 (Item 4884)
      - Community College Conference, Community Colleges NYSUT 79, 1979 (Item 5139)
      - Community College Conference [Includes but may not be limited to:] Deedy, Kenneth; Hobart, Tom; Stollar, Lou; Polishook, Irwin, Mar 1979 (Item 5139)
      - Student Legislature, Dec 1979 (Item 3713)
      - Special Arts Festival, WIZ Banquet, Dec 1979 (Item 4466)
      - Bodner Scholarship Winners, Rebecca Bunnell, winner; Kevin Goldstein, alt. Winner, 1980 (Item 5298)
      - Community College Conference, Apr 1980 (Item 3243)
      - Community College Conferences, Apr 1980 (Item 5139)
      - Student Interviews, Jun 1980 (Item 2269)
      - Science Congress, preparing for 1981 Science Congress (Item 3844)
      - Special Arts Festival, Jean Kennedy Smith, 1981 National Chairman, Very Special Arts Festival (Item 4466)
      - Community Colleges, Feb 1981 (Item 5139)
      - Community College Conference, Apr 1981 (Item 3243)
      - United University Professions PACE (Project For Adult College Education) [Includes but may not be limited to:] Brockport UUP, Apr 1981 (Item 5321)
      - Community College Conference [Includes but may not be limited to:] Frasca, Dan, May 1981 (Item 3243)
      - School Safety Awards Ceremony, May 1981 (Item 4884)
      - School Safety Press Conference, Mayor Koch, Sep 1981 (Item 4884)
      - Newspaper Advisors Conference, New York Times Carol Zack [demonstrates layout techniques to school newspaper advisors], Nov 1981 (Item 3830)
      - Eli Whitney Vocational HS [Connecticut?], picketing re: fired teacher, Jan 1982 (Item 5507)
      - Student Demonstration in Washington DC against budget cuts, testimony against Reaganomics, Feb 1982 (Item 3920)
      - Eli Whitney Vocational HS [Connecticut?], Suffport Tom Mantagnino, Feb 1982 (Item 5507)
      - Community College Conference, 1984 (Item 5139)
      - Community College Conference, 1986 (Item 3243)
      - Levine, Abe and Al Shanker and elementary school students, undated (Item 112)
      - Teacher-Parent protest at "School With Hope", undated (Item 170)
      - Racial isolation in the schools, undated (Item 196)
      - Crisis Schools, undated (Item 223)
      - School Conditions (Bad), undated (Item 391)
      - Student Protest Demonstrations, undated (Item 416)
      - Junior High School, students in class, undated (Item 433)
      - AFT Freedom Schools Program, undated (Item 480)
      - Student Dismissal from school, undated (Item 573)
      - School yard, public school, undated (Item 1036)
      - German Countryside, University of the Air, undated (Item 1345)
      - Hunter, Doris, paraprofessional with student, undated (Item 1348)
      - Bureau for Speech Improvement teachers at work, undated (Item 1452)
      - "Pupils of the Year" Awards presented by NY State Teachers Association of the Mentally Handicapped, undated (Item 1505)
      - Improving Non-Public Schools Conference, undated (Item 2069)
      - Sonko, Momodou Lamin, Financial Aid sought for young African to go to college, undated (Item 2656)
      - Vocational Schools, Michael Squeglia, undated (Item 2684)
      - Classroom Photos, Marcia Levinson, undated (Item 2896)
      - [Museo Del Barrio, children's art workshops, museum tour, and classroom instruction], undated (Item 2916)
      - Community College Conferences - Onandaga Community College; Suffolk Community College; FIT; Stollar, Lou; Samit, Jack; Sugarman, Vera; Sanders, Dan; Deedy, Kenneth; Wharton, Clifton; Schanfeld, Jack, undated (Item 3243CR)
      - Children, Performances, undated (Item 3490)
      - Kindergarten in North-End Industrial Home, Boston, undated (Item 3630)
      - Overcrowded Classrooms, undated (Item 3741)
      - Classroom Photos, undated (Item 3948)
      - Italian-American, Student Award Winners, undated (Item 4331)
      - Classroom Photos, undated (Item 4453)
      - Special Arts Festival, AFT National Committee on Arts for the Handicapped, undated (Item 4466)
      - Student Exposition on Energy Resources, undated (Item 4538)
      - Spofford Juvenile Detention Center, undated (Item 4565)
      - 900 Schools, School for Pregnant Girls, undated (Item 4662)
      - School Safety, Ed Muir, undated (Item 4884)
      - School Safety, Violence in Schools, undated (Item 4884)
      - Back to School [Includes but may not be limited to:] McGinn, Bill; Altomare, George; Silverstein, Evelyn, undated (Item 4917)
      - Back to School, undated (Item 4940)
      - Classroom Photos, undated (Item 5057)
      - Community College Conferences - Kibbee, Robert; Sanders, Dan; FIT; Parkas, Judith, undated (Item 5139CR)
      - Energy, Cortese judging entries in 5th annual poster contest on conservation, undated (Item 5214)
      - Public Schools (Various), undated (Item 5223)
      - Alternative Schools, undated (Item 5223)
      - Handicapped Essay Contest, undated (Item 5241)
      - Ideas in the Classroom, Charles Kolataze - Bartok Celebration, 5/17, undated (Item 5401)
      - National Energy Foundation Day student science projects, undated (Item 5440)
      - New York Alliance for Public Schools, undated (Item 5640)
      - Classroom Scene, undated (Item 5649)
      - SVA's (Student Vocational Assistants), undated (Item 5660)
      - Social Studies [Conference], undated (Item 5673)
      - Very Special Arts Festival, undated (Item 5688)
    - Sub-subseries I:M:2: Teachers
      - Playground Teachers meeting, Jun 15, 1964 (Item 748)
      - JHS Substitute Teachers, "What Goes on Here", Sep 1964 (Item 760)
      - Teachers in Favor of Decentralization with Ralph Poynter and Joe Laspro, May 22, 1968 (Item 591)
      - Music Teachers Convention, Concord Hotel, Nov 28, 1971 (Item 1649)
      - Bilingual Teachers Press Conference, May 1972 (Item 1861)
      - Women Educators Annual Meeting, Oct 14, 1972 (Item 2046)
      - Reinstatement for Fired Teachers (Susquehanna Valley), Jun 1973 (Item 2581)
      - Teacher of the Year, 1974 (Item 2964)
      - Tom, Vivian, Teacher of the Year 1974 Ceremonies and Reception (Item 2993)
      - Binghamton Teachers Conference Day, Jun 1974 (Item 3074)
      - Ludwig, Robert, Teacher of the Year, Nov 1974 (Item 3393)
      - Phipps, Nathaniel, 'Teacher of the Year', 1976 (Item 4003)
      - Marcellus BOE, teachers Barbara Meighan and Erick Pearlstein have to say about being laid off, Apr 1976 (Item 4393)
      - Bronx Teacher, 92 year old, May 1976 (Item 4231)
      - Teacher Art at the Metropolitan, May 1976 (Item 4387)
      - Probationary Teachers appeals panels, Dec 1977 (Item 4854)
      - 1978 STA NYS Conference, Science Teachers Association of NYS (Item 4997)
      - Teacher of the Year 1979, Lucinda Hebbeler (Item 2964)
      - Teacher of the Year, Poster Teacher 1980 (Item 2964)
      - Teacher of the Year, Biology Teacher of the Year 1980 Gene P. Kingham (Item 2964)
      - Teacher of the Year NYS 1980, Jay Sommer (Item 2964)
      - Per Diem Substitutes, Hearings: 1980 Kafka and Swaim (Item 5297)
      - Teachers and the Community, Terry Germaine, Feb 1980 (Item 2483)
      - Teacher of the Year Honored, Lucinda Hebbeler, Feb 25, 1980 (Item 2964)
      - Bilingual Teachers, Betty Holmes, Milady Baez, PTA Pres. Ruth Perez, Feb 1981 (Item 4761)
      - Weinman, Gloria reading teachers first meeting re: closed exams and legislation, Oct 1981 (Item 5342)
      - Teacher of the Year in NYS 1982, Thomas Wagner (Item 2964)
      - NYS Industrial Arts Association, Stan Damast named teacher of the year for 1982 (Item 5229)
      - Damast, Stan, NYS Industrial Arts Association Teacher of the Year, 1982 (Item 5529)
      - Teacher Burn-Out, 2/21/82 edition - 4 individuals, Feb 21, 1982 (Item 5519)
      - Teacher of the Year 1983, Stewart Bogdanoff (Item 2964)
      - Teacher of the Year, 85 runner up Naomi Kirsh, 1985 (Item 2993)
      - Portraits of teachers, undated (Item 152)
      - Teachers face jail, undated (Item 201)
      - Patel, Thelma, NYS. Teacher of the Year, undated (Item 2248)
      - Teachers and the Community, Teacher in the news, undated (Item 2483)
      - Teachers and the Community, Star Lake, NY, undated (Item 2483)
      - Teacher of the Year runners up, undated (Item 2964)
      - Special Physical Education Outstanding Teachers, undated (Item 4531)
      - Lay-Offs, Laid Off Teachers, undated (Item 4690)
      - Music and Physical Education Teachers, Shanker speaking, undated (Item 4800)
      - Stamp Collector Teacher, undated (Item 5170)
      - Business Education Teachers, undated (Item 5238)
      - Substitute Teachers, undated (Item 5247)
      - Per Diem Substitutes, legislation signed by Carey, right to organize for collective bargaining, undated (Item 5297)
      - Per Diem Substitutes, Feldman, Swaim, Alexander, Kafka, undated (Item 5297)
      - Katz, Joseph, Teacher Burn-Out, undated (Item 5519)
      - Freudenberger, Herbert, Teacher Burn-Out, undated (Item 5519)
      - Grayzel, Estherann F., Teacher Burn-Out, undated (Item 5519)
      - Madonna, G. Terry, Teacher Burn-Out, undated (Item 5519)
      - Ryan, Joseph named Outstanding American History Teacher in NYS by the state division of the Daughters of the American Revolution. Also a member of the Faculty Association of Montrose., undated (Item 5530)
      - Unidentified Pictures (Teachers, Black) Plus Dorothy Suecoff, undated (Item 5641)
  - Subseries I:N: Retired Teachers.
    - Atkins, Robert, TRB [Teachers Retirement Board?] swearing in, May 25, 1964 (Item 131)
    - Teachers Retirement System, Teacher-members, Apr 29, 1968 (Item 531)
    - Retired Teachers Meeting, May 18, 1968 (Item 592)
    - Mitchell, Reuben (Teachers Retirement Board Swearing In), 1970 (Item 1075)
    - Retired Teachers Meeting, Peter Bermuth, speaker, Nov 1970 (Item 592)
    - Retired Teachers Meeting, Mar 9, 1971 (Item 592)
    - Retired Teachers Chapter, Apr 1971 (Item 1742)
    - State Retirement Board Meeting, Nov 1971 (Item 1906)
    - Retired Teachers Meeting, Nov 9, 1971 (Item 592)
    - Retired Teachers Luncheon, 1972 (Item 1876)
    - Retired Teachers Meeting, Irving Saul, speaker, Feb 8, 1972 (Item 592)
    - Retired Teachers Meeting, May 1972 (Item 592)
    - Retired Teachers Meeting, Dec 1972 (Item 592)
    - Retired Teachers Meeting, Margery Gross, Executive Secretary, Alliance for a Safer City; Sarah Wiener; Sylvia R. Levinson; Stella Hetden, Dec 12, 1972 (Item 2129)
    - Retired Teachers Luncheon, 1973 (Item 1876)
    - Retired Teachers Meeting, Jan 9, 1973 (Item 592)
    - Retired Teachers Meeting, Feb 13, 1973 (Item 592)
    - Tyler, Gus speaking to retired teachers chapter, Mar 13, 1973 (Item 2271)
    - Mitchell, Reuben being sworn in as a member of the teacher retirement board., May 1973 (Item 2486)
    - York State Manor, Retired Teachers, Oct 1973 (Item 2615)
    - District 14, election endorsee Korpeck for retirement board post, Oct 1973 (Item 2736)
    - Goldberg, Bernard, sworn in as member of the Teachers Retirement System, Nov 11, 1973 (Item 41)
    - Retired Teachers Luncheon, 1974 (Item 1876)
    - Retired Teachers, Fifty Year Members Honored, May 1974 (Item 3113)
    - Retired Teachers Meeting, Nov 1974 (Item 592)
    - NYS Teachers Retirement System delegates annual meeting, Nov 1974 (Item 3334)
    - Retired Teachers Luncheon, 1975 (Item 1876)
    - Retired Teachers Luncheon, May 1975 (Item 3715)
    - Shanker, Al agrees to invest NY Teachers' Retirement System Funds for Big Mac Bonds, Oct 1975 (Item 4110)
    - Retired Teachers Meeting, Nov 1975 (Item 592)
    - Retired Teachers, receive Charter from National Council of Senior Citizens, Nov 1975 (Item 4011)
    - Retired Teachers Luncheon, May 1976 (Item 3715)
    - New York City Teachers Retirement System Candidates, May 1976 (Item 4108)
    - Retirement Forums, May 1976 (Item 4255)
    - NY Teachers' Retirement System Debating Retirement Issues, May 1976 (Item 4283)
    - Retired Teachers Annual Luncheon, 17th luncheon, Carl Megel addresses (AFT), May 1976 (Item 4386)
    - Mitchell, Reuben re-elected to serve fourth three-year term on NYC retirement board, May 1976 (Item 4416)
    - Retired Teachers Meeting, Nov 1976 (Item 592)
    - Teachers Retirement System (NY State), Nov 1976 (Item 4706)
    - Retired Teachers Meeting, Mar 27, 1977 (Item 592)
    - Retired Teachers Meeting, 1978 (Item 592)
    - State Retirement Convention [Includes but may not be limited to:] Pietrantoni, Jeanette, 1978 (Item 5111)
    - State Retirement Convention, 1978 (Item 5126)
    - Teachers Retirement Board Meeting, May 1978 (Item 1121)
    - Retired Teachers Meetings [Includes but may not be limited to:] Cymberg, Shirley, 1979 (Item 592)
    - Retired Teachers, Staff, 1979 (Item 3113)
    - Orazio, Angelo, LI Presidents Council Assemblyman with Retired Teachers for pension benefits 1979 (Item 5148)
    - New York State Teachers Retirement System Convention [Includes but may not be limited to:] Pietrantoni, Jeanette; Maletta, Nick; Korpeck, Hiram; Silverman, Dorothy; Karasik, Alan, 1979 (Item 5221)
    - Retired Teachers, Toast Learning Center, Jan 1979 (Item 5007)
    - Retired Teachers Luncheon, May 1979 (Item 3715)
    - Retired Teachers, Bronx Retired Teachers with Mario Raimo / Simon, May 1979 (Item 5007)
    - Emery, James L. with Kafka, Retired Teacher Pension Legislation, Jun 1979 (Item 3237)
    - Retired Teachers, Florida Chapter, Jun 1979 (Item 5007)
    - Retired Teachers, LI Lobbying for pension improvements, Jun 1979 (Item 5007)
    - Retired Teachers, at City Council, Jun 1979 (Item 5007)
    - NYS Teachers Retirement System convention, Nov 1979 (Item 3334)
    - New York State Teachers Retirement System Board, Re-elect Korpeck, Dec 1979 (Item 5221)
    - York State Manor, Retired Teachers, 1980 (Item 2615)
    - Aaronson, Mel sworn in as teacher-member NYC Retirement Board, 1980 (Item 4896)
    - Retired Teachers Exec. Ed Meeting, May 1980 (Item 592)
    - Retired Teachers, Learning Center, May 1980 (Item 3113)
    - Retirement Meetings, Manhattan, May 1980 (Item 4255)
    - NYSUT Task Force on Retired Teachers, Mel Aaronson, May 1980 (Item 5056)
    - Retired Teachers, Learning Center, Jun 1980 (Item 3113)
    - Retired Teachers Volunteer Party [Includes but may not be limited to:] Aaronson, Mel, Jun 10, 1980 (Item 5292)
    - Retired Teachers Chapter, National Council of Senior Citizens Convention, Oct 1980 (Item 4011)
    - Retired Teachers General Membership Meeting, Nov 1980 (Item 592)
    - New York State Teachers Retirement System Convention 1980, 11/23-11/24, Nov 23, 1980 (Item 5221)
    - Retired Teachers, Volunteer Party Luncheon, Spring 81, 1981 (Item 3113)
    - New York State Teachers Retirement System Convention 1980, 1981 (Item 5221)
    - RTC [Retired Teachers Chapter] Event Honoring Reuben Mitchell, Jan 1981 (Item 218)
    - Silverman, Dorothy endorsed by NYSUT Retirement Board for re-election, Jan 1981 (Item 4876)
    - Retired Teachers, Youth Employment Conference, Apr 1981 (Item 3113)
    - Retired Teachers, Learning Center Faculty, Apr 1981 (Item 3113)
    - Retired Teachers, Luncheon, May 1981 (Item 3113)
    - Shannon, Joseph, sworn in as Teacher-member of NYC Teachers' Retirement Board, May 1981 (Item 3712)
    - UFT VOTE/COPE, Retired Teachers Chapter, May 1981 (Item 5256)
    - Retired Teachers, Luncheon and 50 Year Members Honored, Jun 1981 (Item 3113)
    - Retired Teachers, Save Our Social Security Rally, Jun 18, 1981 (Item 3113)
    - Social Security, Retired Teachers Chapter, UFT, Save Our Social Security Rally, Jun 18, 1981 (Item 5103)
    - New York City Teachers Retirement System, Board Members, Pension Bill Signing, Jul 1981 (Item 4108)
    - DeMarco, Michael, Councilman with RTC [Retired Teacher Chapter] leaders, Aug 1981 (Item 2549)
    - Retired Teachers, Learning Center, Jan 1982 (Item 3113)
    - Korpeck, Hiram, RA, Endorsement backing him for re-election to NYSTRS [New York State Teachers Retirement System], Mar 1982 (Item 2084)
    - Retired Teachers Chapter Annual Luncheon, Jun 1982 (Item 3113)
    - Retired Teachers Chapter, Sep 26, 1982 (Item 3113)
    - Retired Teachers Meeting, Queens, 1986 (Item 592)
    - Mitchell, Reuben, being sworn in as TRB [Teachers Retirement Board?] by Donovan, undated (Item 167)
    - Retired Teachers Chapter Luncheon, undated (Item 167)
    - UFT Retired Teachers Chapter Legislative Committee, undated (Item 168)
    - Wittes, David with Joseph Perrini, Al Shanker, and others receiving award from Teachers Retirement Board, undated (Item 1706)
    - Wittes, David with T. Scott, Secretary, NYC Teachers Retirement Board, undated (Item 1706)
    - NYS Teachers' Retirement Board Members, undated (Item 1751)
    - NYS Teacher Retirement delegates, Al Shanker speaker, undated (Item 2067)
    - Retired Teachers Learning Center, Elmer Spiegler, undated (Item 3113)